zerista.com 2019-11-30

# Simpleview | Privacy Notice

_Last updated: 11/01/2019_

To review historical copies of our privacy policy, contact [privacy@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:privacy@simpleviewinc.com).

Simpleview complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom and Switzerland to the United States in reliance on Privacy Shield. Simpleview has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such information. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

This Privacy Policy explains the types of personal information we collect through our website, [www.simpleviewinc.com](https://barberstock-simpleview.simpleviewcms.com/), how we use it, what we do not do with it, how you can view your information and update it, and how we keep it safe. As a global organization, information about you may be shared globally throughout Simpleviews worldwide organization. See the list of [Simpleview Companies](https://www.simpleviewinc.com/privacy-notice/entities/) and locations.

#####   
Americas

Simpleview LLC  
VisitApps LLC  
Barberstock Systems ULC  
Simpleview Jackrabbit LLC

#####   
**Contact Information**

#####   
**What Information Do We Collect About You?**

User Data/Data Collection: Personal Identification Information  
User Data/Data Collection: Non-personal identification information  
User Data/Data Collection: Web Browser Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies  
User Data/Data Collection: Mobile Applications & Location Awareness  
User Data/Data Collection: Social Media (Features) and Widgets  
User Data/Data Collection: Automated Decision Making and Profiling

#####   
**How Do We Use Your Information?**

Use of Information  
Links to Other Websites/Third Party Disclosure  
Data Collection For Clients and Partners  
California Privacy (CCPA)

#####   
**How Do We Protect Your Information**

Data Security  
Reviewing/Updating Your Information  
Dispute Resolution  
Changes to This Privacy Policy  
Report Concerns

8950 N. Oracle Road  
Tucson, AZ 85704  
+1 520.575.1151

For questions about privacy and data collection through [www.simpleviewinc.com](http://www.simpleviewinc.com/), contact [privacy@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:privacy@simpleviewinc.com).

Simpleview employees are authorized to access personal information only to the extent necessary to serve the applicable purpose(s) and to perform their job functions.

**User Data/Data Collection: Personal Identification Information**

We do not collect any personal information through [www.simpleviewinc.com](http://www.simpleviewinc.com/) except that knowingly and willingly supplied by the visitor for the purpose of providing the services/information requested through our site. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Personal identifying information may be collected through e-newsletter forms, online request forms, contests, feedback forms, surveys, personal interest forms, and mobile application forms. Any information that the customer provides, such as name, address, email, ZIP code, gender, and income will be stored in a secure location and will be used only for those purposes stated. When you choose to submit such information, you are transferring that information into the United States of America and are consenting to such transfer. All data transferred will be/is encrypted (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure, or HTTPS) transfer, through Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Visitors can always refuse to supply personal identification information, noting that choosing to do so may prevent the user from engaging in certain site-related activities. Users of our services, such as e-newsletter subscriptions, may also withdraw consent for the use of their personal information at any time. To review, update, or delete your collected data, or to withdraw consent for use, contact [privacy@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:privacy@simpleview.com).

**User Data/Data Collection: Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. We collect the domain name from each site visitor as well as statistical information, such as the number of visitors and the pages viewed. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer being use, and technical information about the user’s means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

**User Data/Data Collection: Web Browser Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Our site may use "cookies", tags, or scripts to enhance user experience, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base. You will have the option to choose whether to “opt in” for the use of “cookies” when you access the site. If you do choose to allow the use of the “cookies”, you may, at any time, choose to “opt out” of the use of the “cookies.”

A user's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. In these cases, please note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

**User Data/Data Collection:** **Mobile Applications & Location Awareness**

VisitApps, a Simpleview company, collects some personal and location information for the function of mobile applications, if the application user opts in. Any information that the customer provides, such as name, address, email, ZIP code, gender, and income will be stored in a secure location and will be used only for those purposes expressly stated. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, understanding that choosing to do so may prevent the user from engaging in certain mobile application activities. Our Destination Marketing Organisation clients who provide VisitApps mobile apps to customers, can collect registration and form information from the mobile applications upon the user’s agreement via opt-in. Location information is collected if the user agrees to show their location or check-in to venues by GPS.

**User Data/Data Collection: Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

Our website includes social media programs and features, such as Simpleview UGC powered by Stackla, the Facebook Like button and widgets, and the Share button. If you choose to use these features, they may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. The : social media programs, features, and widgets we use are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature(s).

**User Data/Data Collection:** **Automated Decision Making and Profiling**

Simpleview partners with companies that utilize automated decision making processes, including user profiling, in order to provide more relevant marketing materials to those users who opt in to receiving emails from us.

**Use of Information**

The information that we collect is used to enhance the usability and improve the content of our web pages. It may be used to personalize information and for statistical purposes. Personal information will not be shared with third parties unless indicated and when approved by the user (in other words, if the user opts-in to sharing information) or unless required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, court orders, legal process from law enforcement agencies, or similar legal proceedings. We provide information to investigate or prevent suspected illegal activities. Personal data may be shared in the following situations, as well:

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, legal proceedings, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, and
  * To a third party with your prior consent to do so.

Simpleview will retain personal data we process until the visitor/user notifies us that he/she no longer wishes to receive the services or information for which the data was collected. Simpleview will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Links to Other Websites/Third Party Disclosure**

[www.simpleviewinc.com](https://www.simpleviewinc.com/) contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the information collection processes on these sites and cannot control how the information is used. Please view the privacy policies on these other websites for further information.

**Data Collection For Clients and Partners**

Simpleview supports the development and operation of [partner services/products](https://www.simpleviewinc.com/our-world/partners/) that interact with client user information. We request that our partners meet industry standards for security data storage and maintenance equivalent to those that we uphold or higher in regards to any data collected by our partners or by Simpleview in conjunction with these partner services/products. Where applicable, we enter into binding agreements ensuring all parties meet minimum data security standards.

We acknowledge that we may face liability in cases where there is an onward transfer of your personal information from us to a third party. We hold those third parties with whom we do business to the same rigorous security standards that we impose on ourselves

**California Privacy (CCPA)**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Simpleview, or its subsidiaries to a third party for the third party’s direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:privacy@simpleviewinc.com) or write to us:

**Simpleview**  
8950 N. Oracle Road  
Tucson, AZ 85704  
+1 520.575.1151  

**Data Security**

Simpleview employs processes intended to protect user information and maintain security of data. We seek to protect our servers by locating them in areas with documented security procedures, by using firewalls, and by implementing other security technologies. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data. However, despite our preventative measures and those of our partners, NO GUARANTEE CAN BE MADE THAT YOUR INFORMATION AND DATA WILL BE SECURE FROM INTRUSIONS AND UNAUTHORIZED RELEASE TO THIRD PARTIES.

**Reviewing/Updating Your Information**

You have the right to review your information at any time. If you would like to review your information within our contacts database, update it, or remove it, please contact [privacy@simpleviewinc.com](mailto:privacy@simpleviewinc.com).

If you would like to be removed from or change your subscriptions to any of our newsletters, there is a link at the bottom of every newsletter that allows you to do so.

**Dispute Resolution**

Under certain circumstances, an individual may be allowed to invoke binding arbitration for a violation of that individual’s privacy rights.

We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change and update our privacy policy. Any changes to our policy will be prominently posted on this site. Last updated: 6/24/2019

**Report Concerns**

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.
